myadcorner.com 2016-11-21

# Privacy And Policy - Bookmyad

### Privacy And Policy

We value your trust with BOOKMYAD and we promise to protect your privacy at all costs. However, we would still want you to read the following policy to figure out how we process your personal information before you utilize our website. 

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you need to enter your name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
• To personalize your experience (your information helps to respond to your individual needs in a better manner)  
• To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings regarding information and feedback received from your end)  
• To improve customer service (your information galvanizes us to respond more effectively to your customer service requests and support needs)  
• To process transactions, your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. • To send periodic email. The email address you provide may be used to send you information. You are requested to respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.  

#### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers’ database only. It can be accessed by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and they in turn are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes, we do use cookies for improving the responsiveness of the sites for our users. Cookies are small files transferred through a site or its service provider to your computer’s hard drive via your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service provider systems to recognize your browser; and as a result capture and remember certain information. With the help of cookies, we are able to assign a unique random number (User ID) as user identification by collecting information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you every time a cookie is sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting directly through our customer service. 

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personal information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe that the release is appropriate and in compliance with the law. Further, our site’s policies should also be fulfilled. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

####  Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website.

#### Terms and Conditions

By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access the Website. Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.bookmyad.com/tnc.jsp 

#### User’s Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. As a user, you also agree to the collection and utilization of the information disclosed on the website from your end. 

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

Changes to our privacy policy will be disclosed on this page. Any changes to our privacy policy will be directly communicated through our website at least ten days prior to its implementation. You should consistently check this section, in case of any updates or changes regarding the present terms and conditions. 

#### User’s Feedback

We welcome questions and comments related to our privacy policy from our users. You can get in touch with us through the Feedback link offered on our website.
